tacticalgear.com 2019-04-20

# Privacy Policy | Tactical Gear Superstore | TacticalGear.com

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. We utilize military-grade security and encryption technology to ensure that your personal and financial information remains private and safe. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the TacticalGear.com web site. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages include:

  * Name
  * User ID (if you have an account with us)
  * Password (if you have an account with us)
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order merchandise and want it sent to a third party, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address (if different from your own)

## The Way We Use the Information

TacticalGear.com will use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. This information is not shared with or sold to outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. Billing information is transmitted to our payment processor over a highly secure 128-bit encryption, ensuring that your information will not be intercepted by a third party.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We utilize a "Recommend this page" script which allows you to direct other people to certain pages within our web site. This script collects your name and email address as well as the name(s) and email address(es) of the person(s) you enter into the form. This information is collected for the sole purpose of sending an email and is not recorded in any database or mailing list.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site and improve your shopping experience. This information in no way identifies you personally. This information may be shared with outside parties for the purpose of enhancing our service.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to help protect your order information. This encrypts your credit/debit card number, order information and other personal information. When you access our cart and checkout pages, your computer automatically uses SSL encryption to communicate with our server. You easily can verify that this encryption is taking place by looking at the web address (URL) in your browser window. The address will begin with "https://" when your information is being protected by SSL encryption (the "s" stands for secure). Most modern browsers also will show a green padlock icon.

To further ensure the security of your personal data, we do not store credit or debit card information on our servers. During checkout, your credit card information bypasses our systems completely and goes directly to our payment service provider, Braintree. A division of PayPal, Braintree utilizes some of most advanced security features in the payment processing industry and is a verified Level 1 PCI-compliant processor. Please click here to learn more about [Braintree](https://www.braintreepayments.com/products-and-features/data-security).

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by using the "LOGIN" functionality located at the top of most TacticalGear.com web pages. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
